Now I'm going to show you how to prepare your stones.
When you get a stone you would receive in a box and it would also come with a nylon scraper.
It would be a white very white color stone.
The first thing we want to do is rinse it in warm water.
This does not need to be soaked.
We do not recommend suds, soap or detergent, or dish washer for your stone.
After your first use of your stone, you would use the nylon scraper that comes with 4 different corners to clean your stone.
You would simply scrape any excess food from the stone using this scraper.
Any of these corners would get in to any corner on type of stone that you have.
Then you would just simply rinse it with warm water.
Again we do not recommend any soap.
So you would just rinse it and then store it either back in the box or in your oven.